divinewrite.com 2008-12-17

# Advertising Copywriter, Website Copywriter, SEO Copywriter - Divine Write Copywriting

Divine Write aims to provide you with information on this Website regarding the Products and Services available to you to purchase. To achieve this aim and to fulfill your purchase requirements, we need to make the most efficient use of all personal information that is provided by you to us on a confidential basis.

We are committed to ensuring the confidentiality and privacy of all personal information it collects during the conduct of our business. In relation to managing personal information, we abide by the National Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). 

**What is Personal Information?**

Personal information is any information about a client or individual that identifies that person or by which that person’s identity can be reasonably determined. We recognise that personal information is sensitive and that the provision of such information is an act of trust.

**How do we Collect Personal Information?**

Collection of your personal information such as your email address may be required to enable us to respond to any query that you may have or to enable you to become a member of our website. This personal information will enable us to liaise with you to provide you with the information that you desire and updates when requested. If we do not collect and make use of this personal information, our ability to assist you is greatly limited.

If you wish to purchase Products and/or Services from us we will require you to voluntarily provide us with other personal information such as your full name, address, postcode, contact telephone numbers and credit card details. No matter how your personal information is collected, it will be dealt with by Divine Write in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Where possible, personal information is collected directly from you by your use of our website. In situations where you personally provide us with your personal information will shall imply your consent to our collection on the basis that we have informed you herein what personal information will be recorded and for what purposes.

The credit card payment page hosted on this website is protected by Westpac Banking Corporation's 128-bit encrypted Secure Socket Layer (SSL) certificate.

**How do we Use the Personal Information?**

We use the personal information collected from you to:

  * provide you with information or services at your request; 
  * take purchase orders from you; 
  * dispatch Products and/or Services to you pursuant to our Terms. 
  * register your contact details; and
  * establish and maintain our relationship with you; 

We do not disclose any personal information for any other purposes without your consent unless required by law.

**Direct Marketing**

From time to time we may use your personal information to provide you with updates and new features on our website.

If you do not want to receive any of this information, contact us at one of our offices. If you inform us that you no longer wish to receive information about updates and new features on our website, we will not send you any further material. You can however, change your mind about receiving this information at any time by contacting us.

**Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties**

Divine Write may disclose your personal information in certain circumstances.

Sometimes we are required or authorised by law to disclose your personal information. For example, we may disclose your personal information to a Court in response to a subpoena.

We may also disclose personal information to a party contracted to Divine Write to provide administrative services or other activities on our behalf. In those circumstances that party is bound by the same privacy rules we follow.

**Ensuring your personal information is up-to-date**

We rely on personal information we hold about you to efficiently conduct our business of providing you with the products/services purchased by you. Therefore, it is important that the personal information collected is accurate, complete and up-to-date. If you think we have incorrectly recorded your personal information please contact us so we can correct that information.

**Security of Your Personal Information**

We take all reasonable precautions to safeguard personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure are taken as follows:

  * external and internal premises security
  * restricted access to personal information
  * confidentiality agreements with contractors and third party organisations
  * maintaining technology products to prevent unauthorised computer access

In most cases, a summary of your personal information held by us, such as your name and address details, contact telephone numbers, are freely available to you by calling one of our offices.

All requests for access to personal information will be handled as quickly as possible and we shall endeavor to process any request for access within 30 days of having received the request. 

Divine Write may be required by law to retain personal information for a period of time after you have ceased your relationship with us. 

Divine Write is not always required to provide access to personal information upon request.

Access may be refused in a number of circumstances such as:

  * where the information may relate to existing or anticipated legal proceedings
  * where required or authorised by law 
  * where the request is regarded as frivolous or vexatious

If access is denied, we will explain why.

**Identification**

A Commonwealth identifier is a Commonwealth Government or Commonwealth Government agency designated identification number such as your Tax File Number (TFN) or Medicare number.

Divine Write does not use Commonwealth identifiers as a means of identifying the personal information that we may have collected about you.

**Sensitive Information**

Divine Write does not collect sensitive information. Any information provided by you in this regard will not be recorded or retained by Divine Write unless your consent is provided.

**Access via the Internet**

The Internet has brought many improvements in the way Divine Write is able to do business. Divine Write is continually maintaining and upgrading technology and procedures in this respect to its online transactions. 

Divine Write retains the right to collect any information from any visitor to our Divine Write website regarding the visitor’s use of our website typically but not exclusively for the better understanding of our visitors. For example, how often a visitor goes to a specific page can assist us in focusing our business to the interests and needs of our visitors, thereby improving the services available to you. Any visitor to the Divine Write website who provides any information to Divine Write in this regard agrees that Divine Write has the right to use that information and agrees that this information shall be deemed to be non-confidential. 

We may compile a report identifying the number of visitors to the homepage of our website and other particulars pages on our website. These reports may be shared with sponsors and prospective sponsors of our website, but they will not disclose any personal information.

Divine Write like a number of other commercial websites stores information in a small text file on your hard disk known as a cookie. The information stored in the cookie includes your preferences and choices you make while visiting the Divine Write website. Please check your web browser to ensure that you have consented to the use of cookies during your web browsing. Please note that we do need cookies for you to be able to properly access our website.

**Privacy Policy changes**

Divine Write constantly reviews all its policies and procedures to keep up-to-date with changes in the law, technology and market practice.

As a result we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time.

This Privacy Policy was last amended 14 August, 2008.

**Concerns or requests for access?**

If you have a question about this Privacy Policy, wish to lodge a request to access information, or lodge a complaint, you can contact our Privacy Officer at info@divinewrite.com.
